module.exports = {
  questions,
  rightAns,
};

export const questions = [
  {
    question: 'what is and african meal ',
    answers: ['Donner', 'Achu', 'kayam', 'spines'],
  },
  {
    question: ' Most sexy woman ',
    answers: ['Beyounce', 'Ben ', 'Lucy', 'Joy'],
  },
  {
    question: ' How much is my tv',
    answers: ['100 euros ', '200 euros', '20 euros ', '10 euros '],
  },
  {
    question: ' whats the name of my first girl friend ',
    answers: [' Ann', ' Eqios', 'Beryl', ' Ogo'],
  },
  {
    question: 'who develop facebook',
    answers: ['Mark zukenberg', 'etoo', 'messi', 'ricky'],
  },
  {
    question: ' whats the name of my mama ',
    answers: ['justine ', 'kate ', 'mama', 'joy'],
  },
  {
    question: 'How old is Neymar',
    answers: ['1', '30', '29', '9'],
  },
  {
    question: 'Is  and African country',
    answers: ['Cameroon', 'Germany', 'Spain', 'France '],
  },
  {
    question: 'who develop Instagram',
    answers: ['Mark zukenberg', 'etoo', 'messi', 'ricky'],
  },
  {
    question: 'Best fotballer in ther world ? ',
    answers: ['ronaldo', 'etoo', 'messi', 'ricky'],
  },
];

export const rightAns = [1, 2, 4, 2, 4, 2, 1, 2, 3, 2];
